http://www.newberry.org/privacy

Jump to navigation
Donate Now
Join the Mailing List
Search this site
HomeVisitResearch VisitsAttend Programs and EventsVisit an ExhibitionBook FairBughouse Square DebatesTours and OrientationsGroup Visits to the Reading RoomsLocation and HoursDirectionsAccommodations and DiningRules of ConductPlan an EventWeddingsSocial Events and CelebrationsCorporate EventsNon Profit/Academic EventsEvent SpacesFrequently Asked QuestionsBookshopAboutHistoryCollection HistoryTimelineLand AcknowledgmentFollow the NewberryNewsAnnouncementsBlogs and PodcastsNewberry MagazinePress RoomStaff/Dept. DirectoryFocus on ConservationFocus on Collection ServicesFocus on FacilitiesStaff BiographiesBoard of TrusteesOpportunitiesEmploymentInternshipsVolunteeringCollecting at the NewberryCollecting EmphasesResearchCore CollectionsAmerican History and CultureAmerican Indian and Indigenous StudiesChicago and the MidwestGenealogy and Local HistoryHistory of the BookModern Manuscripts and ArchivesMaps, Travel, and ExplorationMedieval, Renaissance, and Early Modern StudiesPerforming ArtsPostcardsReligionCatalogs and GuidesOnline CatalogModern Manuscript CollectionsResearch GuidesDatabasesDigital NewberryDigital Resources by TypeServices for Readers and ResearchersGetting Your Reader's CardMaking an Appointment for the Reading RoomsReading Room PoliciesReading Room ProceduresRights and ReproductionsInterlibrary LoanReferralsContact a LibrarianNewberry Institute for Research and EducationOpportunities for UndergraduatesScholar-in-ResidenceGraduate Scholar-in-ResidenceNewberry Institute NewsResearch CentersCenter for American Indian and Indigenous StudiesCenter for the History of CartographyCenter for Renaissance StudiesChicago StudiesFellowshipsLong-Term FellowshipsShort-Term FellowshipsPublication SubventionHow to ApplyNewberry FellowsPrograms and EventsPrograms for the PublicMeet the AuthorNewberry ColloquiumConversations at the NewberryBook FairBughouse Square DebatesGenealogyPast Public Programs: Watch and ListenExhibitionsPast ExhibitionsAdult Education SeminarsSeminar ScheduleRegistration InformationVirtual Seminars FAQSeminar Policies and ProceduresTeach a SeminarTeacher and Student ProgramsDigital Collections for the ClassroomNewberry Teachers’ Consortium: Professional Development SeminarsResources for Remote Teaching and LearningOpportunities for Chicago Public School TeachersTeacher Programs FellowshipsOther Programs for TeachersPrograms for StudentsPrograms for GenealogistsGenealogy BlogScholarly SeminarsRegistration InformationSeminar Proposal FormAmerican Art and Visual Culture SeminarAmerican Literature SeminarAmerican Political Thought SeminarBorderlands and Latino/a Studies SeminarBritish History SeminarChicago: City of Commerce and Design, 1890-1990 SeminarEighteenth-Century SeminarEuropean Art SeminarGender and Sexuality SeminarGerman Studies SeminarHistory of Capitalism SeminarIrish Studies SeminarLabor History SeminarMilton SeminarNAIS Working GroupPremodern Studies SeminarReligion and Culture in the Americas SeminarUrban History Dissertation GroupWriting History SeminarCenter for American Indian and Indigenous Studies ProgramsNAIS Working GroupNCAIS Graduate Student ConferenceNCAIS Spring Workshop in Research MethodsNCAIS Summer InstituteNEH Summer ProgramsPast McNickle Programs: Watch and ListenCenter for Renaissance Studies ProgramsGraduate ProgramsEighteenth-Century SeminarMilton SeminarSeminar in European ArtPremodern Studies SeminarMellon Summer Institutes in Vernacular PaleographyOther Renaissance ProgramsPast ProgramsCenter for the History of Cartography ProgramsKenneth Nebenzahl, Jr., LecturesNEH Summer ProgramsChicago Map Society MeetingsPast ProgramsChicago Studies ProgramsEvents for DonorsFundraising EventsGiveAnnual Support and MembershipNewberry AssociatesPresident's FellowsNext ChapterGiving SocietiesPlanned GivingBlatchford SocietyMeet Our DonorsGoals and BenefitsGifts Anyone Can MakeGifts That Pay You IncomeFor Professional AdvisorsContact UsEvents for DonorsFundraising EventsDonate Books and MaterialsHonor Roll of DonorsShop
Home
VisitResearch Visits
Attend Programs and EventsVisit an Exhibition
Book Fair
Bughouse Square Debates
Tours and OrientationsGroup Visits to the Reading Rooms
Location and HoursDirections
Accommodations and Dining
Press Room
Staff/Dept. DirectoryFocus on ConservationConservation Resources
Recent Projects
Focus on Collection Services
Focus on Facilities
Staff Biographies
Board of Trustees
OpportunitiesEmployment
Internships
VolunteeringBook Fair Volunteering
Digital NewberryDigital Resources by Type
Services for Readers and ResearchersGetting Your Reader's Card
Making an Appointment for the Reading Rooms
Reading Room Policies
Reading Room Procedures
Rights and ReproductionsRights and Reproductions FAQs
Notice and Take-Down Procedure
Warning Concerning Copyright Restrictions
Interlibrary Loan
Referrals
Contact a Librarian
Newberry Institute for Research and EducationOpportunities for UndergraduatesAssociated Colleges of the Midwest
Newberry Library Undergraduate Seminar
Scholar-in-ResidenceCurrent Scholars-in-Residence
Graduate Scholar-in-ResidenceCurrent Graduate Scholars-in-Residence
Newberry Institute News
Research CentersCenter for American Indian and Indigenous StudiesNCAIS Consortium
Programs
Fellowships
Publications
Digital Resources
Center for the History of CartographyPrograms
Calendar
Fellowships
Publications
Teach a Seminar
Teacher and Student ProgramsDigital Collections for the Classroom
Newberry Teachers’ Consortium: Professional Development SeminarsFAQ - NTC Professional Development Seminars
Resources for Remote Teaching and Learning
Opportunities for Chicago Public School Teachers
Teacher Programs Fellowships
Other Programs for Teachers
Programs for Students
Programs for GenealogistsGenealogy Blog
Scholarly SeminarsRegistration Information
Seminar Proposal Form
Writing History Seminar
Center for American Indian and Indigenous Studies ProgramsNAIS Working Group
NCAIS Graduate Student Conference
NCAIS Spring Workshop in Research Methods
NCAIS Summer Institute
NEH Summer Programs
Past McNickle Programs: Watch and Listen
Center for Renaissance Studies ProgramsGraduate ProgramsGraduate Seminars
Eighteenth-Century Seminar
Milton Seminar
Seminar in European Art
Premodern Studies SeminarPast Premodern Studies Seminars
Mellon Summer Institutes in Vernacular Paleography
Other Renaissance ProgramsCervantes Symposium
Dante Lecture
NEH-Funded Programs
Newberry Consort
Shakespeare Project of Chicago
Past Programs
Center for the History of Cartography ProgramsKenneth Nebenzahl, Jr., Lectures
NEH Summer Programs
Chicago Map Society Meetings
Past Programs
Chicago Studies Programs
Events for Donors
Fundraising Events
GiveAnnual Support and MembershipNewberry Associates
President's Fellows
Privacy
We have created this statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. We do not collect personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. This policy is your guide to how we will handle information we learn about you from your visit to our website.
Throughout our webpages, we provide links to other servers which may contain information of interest to our readers. We take no responsibility for, and exercise no control over, the organizations, privacy policies, views, or accuracy of the information contained on other servers.
Statistics and Data-Tracking
The Newberry may use cookies and other tracking mechanisms to track browsing activity on the Newberry website and the online services we work with in order to assess the navigational structure of our website and, when necessary, make changes that will enhance the user experience. These technologies also allow us to increase the effectiveness of our promotional efforts and, when possible, serve you with sponsored posts regarding our programming and other services on external platforms, such as social media sites. Unless you have initiated an online transaction that involves your disclosure of personal information, we will not have access to your personal information.
Credit Card Security
We care about the safety and security of your transaction. We use a high-grade encryption key (RC4, 128 bit) and the https security protocol to communicate with your browser software. This method is the industry standard security protocol, which makes it extremely difficult for anyone else to intercept the credit card information you send to us. Contributions may also be made by calling us at (312) 255-3544 or delivered directly to the Newberry Development office.
Personal Information
Forms: If you complete any forms on this site and share your personally identifying information, this information will be used only to provide you with more targeted content. We may use your contact information to send further information about our organization or to contact you when necessary. You may always opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the “Opt Out” section below. We do not share or sell your contact information
Email: You also may decide to send us personally identifying information via email containing a question or comment. We use personally identifying information from email primarily to respond to your requests. We may forward your email to other employees who are better able to answer your questions. We may also use your email to contact you in the future about our programs that may be of interest.
We want to be very clear: We will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. Except as might be required by law, we do not share any personally identifying information we receive with any outside parties.
If you sign up for one or more of our email lists, you can always unsubscribe from receiving particular types of communications, or opt out of receiving all communications from the Newberry. We will not share your name or email address with any outside parties.
Opt Out or Change Your Contact Information
Change Your Contact Preferences - Our site provides users the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us through an online form. You may choose to receive only specific communications or none at all. You may use the same form to change your contact information if you wish to continue receiving mailings.
Share This Page
